Guide to the Duke University Progress Pictures Collection, 1925-1932
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- West Campus
  - 19290729WC0233.jpg (Image 390)
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building, Group "C" Dormitories and part of the Auditorium Building.
    - Union
  - 19290729WC0234.jpg (Image 391)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from Quadrangle showing Law Building and Library.
    - Law
  - 19290729WC0235.jpg (Image 392)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from court and of Group "B" Dormitory, showing part of Group "B" Dormitory and Group "C" Dormitory.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290729WC0236.jpg (Image 393)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from court end of Group "B" Dormitory showing part of Group "B" Dormitory and Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290729WC0237.jpg (Image 394)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from rear of Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290729WC0238.jpg (Image 395)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from rear of Auditorium Building.
    - Page
  - 19290729WC0239.jpg (Image 396)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19290729WC0240.jpg (Image 397)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from Chapel location showing classroom and Auditorium Building and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19290729WC0241.jpg (Image 398)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View showing first floor of Gymnasium ready for concreting.
    - Gym
  - 19290729WC0242.jpg (Image 399)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View taken from Medical School showing location of Botany and Zoology Building and Physics Building.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19290729WC0243.jpg (Image 400)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View showing Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19290729WC0244a.jpg (Image 401)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View showing Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290729WC0244b.jpg (Image 402)
    - 1929-07-29
    - View showing Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290903WC0245.jpg (Image 403)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from location of Chapel, showing School of Religion.
    - Divinity
  - 19290903WC0246.jpg (Image 404)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from location of Chapel, showing classroom and Auditorium and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19290903WC0247.jpg (Image 405)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from south end of Group "B" Dormitory, showing "B" Dormitory and shovel excavating for the extension to Group "B".
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290903WC0248.jpg (Image 406)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from in front of Medical School and Hospital, showing foundation work for Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19290903WC0249.jpg (Image 407)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from rear of Group "A" Dormitory. The blank wall shows where Group "A" Dormitory extension joins same. Excavation for this shown in foreground.
    - Craven - A
  - 19290903WC0250.jpg (Image 408)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from rear of classroom and Auditorium, showing location of stage. Union Building at right of picture.
    - Page
  - 19290903WC0251.jpg (Image 409)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from the main entrance, showing front of Library and Law Building.
    - Law
  - 19290903WC0252.jpg (Image 410)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from front of Gymnasium, showing part of steel trusses for erection of Gymnasium
    - Gym
  - 19290903WC0253.jpg (Image 411)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View taken from south end of Group "B" Dormitory, showing Group "A" and "B" Dormitories. Medical School can be seen through railway gap.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19290903WC0254.jpg (Image 412)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View of the Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19290903WC0255a.jpg (Image 413)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View of the Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19290903WC0255b.jpg (Image 414)
    - 1929-09-03
    - View of the Stadium, taken from open end of horseshoe.
    - Stadium
  - 19291004WC0256.jpg (Image 415)
    - 1929-10-04
    - Union Building and classroom and Auditorium Building.
    - Law
  - 19291004WC0257.jpg (Image 416)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing foundation for extension to Group "B" Dormitory
    - Crowell - B
  - 19291004WC0258.jpg (Image 417)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing foundation for extension to Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19291004WC0259.jpg (Image 418)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing foundation for extension to Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19291004WC0260.jpg (Image 419)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing front of the Gymnasium Building.
    - Gym
  - 19291004WC0261.jpg (Image 420)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing the rear of classroom and Auditorium Building.
    - Page
  - 19291004WC0262.jpg (Image 421)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19291004WC0263.jpg (Image 422)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View taken from Chapel location showing classroom and Auditorium and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19291004WC0264.jpg (Image 423)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View taken from near front of Medical School and showing Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19291004WC0265.jpg (Image 424)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing Stadium.
    - Stadium
  - 19291004WC0266a.jpg (Image 425)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing Stadium completed.
    - Stadium
  - 19291004WC0266b.jpg (Image 426)
    - 1929-10-04
    - View showing Stadium completed.
    - Stadium
  - 19291108WC0267.jpg (Image 427)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from Medical School and Hospital showing Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19291108WC0268.jpg (Image 428)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing Law Building, Library and Union Building at extreme left.
    - Law
  - 19291108WC0269.jpg (Image 429)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from Chapel location, showing Auditorium Building and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19291108WC0270.jpg (Image 430)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from Chapel location, showing School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19291108WC0271.jpg (Image 431)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View showing rear of classroom and Auditorium Building.
    - Page
  - 19291108WC0272.jpg (Image 432)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View showing front of Gymnasium Building.
    - Gym
  - 19291108WC0273.jpg (Image 433)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing front of Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Craven - A
  - 19291108WC0274.jpg (Image 434)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View showing rear of Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Craven - A
  - 19291108WC0275.jpg (Image 435)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View showing rear of Group "B" Dormitories and Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19291108WC0276.jpg (Image 436)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View showing rear of Group "B" Dormitories and also foundation in front of picture for Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19291108WC0277.jpg (Image 437)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from main Quadrangle showing Group "A" Dormitories on left and Group "B" Dormitories on the right of picture.
    - Craven - A
  - 19291108WC0278.jpg (Image 438)
    - 1929-11-08
    - View taken from location of Physics Building, showing Medical School and Hospital, with Botany and Zoology Building in foreground.
    - Medicine
  - 19291204WC0279.jpg (Image 439)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from Medical School and Hospital, showing Botany and Zoology Building on the left, and Library, Union Building and Group "C" Dormitories on the right.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19291204WC0280.jpg (Image 440)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from Library showing Botany and Zoology Building and Medical School.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19291204WC0281.jpg (Image 441)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from location of Physics Building, showing Law Building and Library Building.
    - Library
    - and Law
  - 19291204WC0282.jpg (Image 442)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from Chapel location showing Auditorium Building and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19291204WC0283.jpg (Image 443)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building.
    - Divinity
  - 19291204WC0284.jpg (Image 444)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from rear of Auditorium showing stage under construction, and Union Building at right.
    - Page
  - 19291204WC0285.jpg (Image 445)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View showing front of Gymnasium Building.
    - Gym
  - 19291204WC0286.jpg (Image 446)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from the south end of Group "B" Dormitories showing Group "B" Dormitories under construction.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19291204WC0287.jpg (Image 447)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from southeast corner of Group "B" Dormitories extension showing court at Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19291204WC0288.jpg (Image 448)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View showing construction of the first floor for Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19291204WC0289.jpg (Image 449)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View showing the end of Group "B" Dormitories and rear of Group "A" Dormitories. Derrick is located in Group "A" Dormitories extension court.
    - Residential
  - 19291204WC0290.jpg (Image 450)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View showing rear of Group "A" Dormitories and Group "A" Dormitories extension.
    - Craven - A
  - 19291204WC0291.jpg (Image 451)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from the front of Group "C" Dormitories showing front of Group "A" and Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Residential
  - 19291204WC0292.jpg (Image 452)
    - 1929-12-04
    - View taken from third floor of Group "B" Dormitories showing front of Group "A" Dormitories, with Medical School and Hospital at the left.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300102WC0293.jpg (Image 453)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from Medical School looking south along main Quadrangle. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Academic
    - view of academic quad
  - 19300102WC0294.jpg (Image 454)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from near front of Law Building, showing Botany and Zoology Building and Medical School. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19300102WC0295.jpg (Image 455)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View showing front of Law Building. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Law
  - 19300102WC0296.jpg (Image 456)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View showing front of Library. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Library
  - 19300102WC0297.jpg (Image 457)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from near end of Group "B" Dormitories, showing extension for Group "A" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Craven - A
  - 19300102WC0298.jpg (Image 458)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View showing extension for Group "B" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Crowell - B
    - extension of Group B dormitories
  - 19300102WC0299.jpg (Image 459)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View showing front of Gymnasium Building. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Gym
  - 19300102WC0300.jpg (Image 460)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View showing rear of classroom and Auditorium Building, showing stage under construction. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Page
  - 19300102WC0301.jpg (Image 461)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from location of Chapel showing School of Religion and Library. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Divinity
  - 19300102WC0302.jpg (Image 462)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from location of Chapel, showing classroom and Auditorium and Union Building. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Page
  - 19300102WC0303.jpg (Image 463)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from front of Group "C" Dormitories, showing front of Group "A" and "B" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Craven - A
  - 19300102WC0304.jpg (Image 464)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle near Union Building showing front of Group "A" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Craven - A
  - 19300102WC0305a.jpg (Image 465)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from south end of Group "B" Dormitories showing extension to Group "B" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300102WC0305b.jpg (Image 466)
    - 1930-01-02
    - View taken from south end of Group "B" Dormitories showing extension to Group "B" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-01-09 on back of photo]
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300205WC0306.jpg (Image 467)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View taken from Medical School, showing Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19300205WC0307.jpg (Image 468)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View taken from main Quadrangle with Medical School on the left.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19300205WC0308.jpg (Image 469)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing foundation for Physics Building and also Botany and Zoology Building and Medical School.
    - Medicine
  - 19300205WC0309.jpg (Image 470)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing front of Law Building.
    - Law
  - 19300205WC0310.jpg (Image 471)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing Library, with Law Building at right.
    - Library
  - 19300205WC0311.jpg (Image 472)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View taken from Chapel location showing classroom and Auditorium Building and Union Building.
    - Page
  - 19300205WC0312.jpg (Image 473)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library.
    - Divinity
  - 19300205WC0313.jpg (Image 474)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing front of Gymnasium Building.
    - Gym
  - 19300205WC0314.jpg (Image 475)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing rear of classroom and Auditorium, with Union Building at right.
    - Page
  - 19300205WC0315.jpg (Image 476)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing extension to Group "A" Dormitory.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300205WC0316.jpg (Image 477)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing extension to Group "B" Dormitories at left of picture and extension to "A" Dormitories at right.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300205WC0317.jpg (Image 478)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing Quadrangle front of Group "A" Dormitories with Group "B" at right.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300205WC0318.jpg (Image 479)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing Group "A" Dormitories at left and "B" Dormitories at right.
    - Residential
  - 19300205WC0319a.jpg (Image 480)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300205WC0319b.jpg (Image 481)
    - 1930-02-05
    - View showing Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300206WC0320.jpg (Image 482)
    - 1930-02-06
    - View taken from the roof of Group "A" Dormitories showing Group "B" Dormitories. [Dated 1930-02-05 on back of photo]
    - Craven - A
  - 19300206WC0321.jpg (Image 483)
    - 1930-02-06
    - View taken from top of Group "A" Dormitories showing Union Building and School or Religion. Classroom and Auditorium at rear of Union Building. [Dated 1930-02-05 on back of photo]
    - Union
  - 19300206WC0322.jpg (Image 484)
    - 1930-02-06
    - View taken from top of Group "A" Dormitories showing Union Building, Library and Medical School. [Dated 1930-02-05 on back of photo]
    - Medicine
  - 19300206WC0323.jpg (Image 485)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View taken from Medical School, looking along axis of campus, showing Botany and Zoology Building in foreground. [Dated on front and back of photo 1930-03-04]
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19300304WC0324.jpg (Image 486)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View taken from in front of the Law Building, showing Botany and Zoology Building and Medical School.
    - Botany/Zoology
  - 19300304WC0325.jpg (Image 487)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View taken from in front of the Library Building showing foundation for Physics Building.
    - Physics
  - 19300304WC0326.jpg (Image 488)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View taken from Chemistry Building location, showing excavation for Chemistry Building and Law Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300304WC0327.jpg (Image 489)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing excavation for Chemistry Building, with Medical School in background.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300304WC0328.jpg (Image 490)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing front of Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300304WC0329.jpg (Image 491)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing front of Group "A" Dormitories and Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Residential
  - 19300304WC0330.jpg (Image 492)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing extension to Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300304WC0331.jpg (Image 493)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing extension to Group "B" Dormitories on left and Group "A" Dormitories on the right of picture.
    - Residential
  - 19300304WC0332.jpg (Image 494)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing front of Gymnasium.
    - Gym
  - 19300304WC0333.jpg (Image 495)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing rear of Auditorium Building, with scaffold around stage.
    - Page
  - 19300304WC0334.jpg (Image 496)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View taken from near the Chapel location, showing excavation for Chapel Building.
    - Chapel
  - 19300304WC0335.jpg (Image 497)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View taken from near the rear of the Chapel, showing foundation excavation for Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19300304WC0336a.jpg (Image 498)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300304WC0336b.jpg (Image 499)
    - 1930-03-04
    - View showing Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300401WC0337.jpg (Image 500)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View taken from top of the Medical School tower looking along Quadrangle.
    - Campus View
    - people
  - 19300401WC0338.jpg (Image 501)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View taken from top of Medical School tower showing Library Building in center of picture and foundation for Chemistry Building at bottom of picture.
    - Campus View
    - law, library from davison
  - 19300401WC0339.jpg (Image 502)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View taken from top of Group "A" Dormitories showing Library in center of picture.
    - Library
  - 19300401WC0340.jpg (Image 503)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View taken from top of Union Building showing Group "A" Dormitories, with Group "B" Dormitories at right of picture.
    - Residential
  - 19300401WC0341.jpg (Image 504)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View looking North, showing Group "B" Dormitories extension and Group "A" Dormitories extension.
    - Residential
  - 19300401WC0342.jpg (Image 505)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View taken from top of School of Religion showing foundation for Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19300401WC0343.jpg (Image 506)
    - 1930-04-01
    - View taken from near the rear of Chapel, showing foundation for same. School of Religion on left and Auditorium on right of picture.
    - Chapel
  - 19300503WC0344.jpg (Image 507)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Library showing front of Physics Building and Botany and Zoology Building.
    - Physics
  - 19300503WC0345.jpg (Image 508)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View showing foundation for Chapel. Forms being built for pouring first floor concrete.
    - Chapel
  - 19300503WC0346.jpg (Image 509)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View showing location of Chapel, taken from main campus.
    - Chapel
  - 19300503WC0347a.jpg (Image 510)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Group "A" Dormitory, showing Union, Library, Law Building and Medical School.
    - Campus View
    - looking towards davison
  - 19300503WC0347b.jpg (Image 511)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Group "A" Dormitory, showing Union, Library, Law Building and Medical School.
    - Campus View
    - looking towards davison
  - 19300503WC0348a.jpg (Image 512)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from rear of Chapel showing foundation for same.
    - Chapel
  - 19300503WC0348b.jpg (Image 513)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from rear of Chapel showing foundation for same.
    - Chapel
  - 19300503WC0349a.jpg (Image 514)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Union Building showing Group "A" and "B" Dormitories.
    - Residential
  - 19300503WC0349b.jpg (Image 515)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Union Building showing Group "A" and "B" Dormitories.
    - Residential
  - 19300503WC0350a.jpg (Image 516)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from south end of Dormitories showing Group "B" Dormitory and Group "A" Dormitory extensions.
    - Campus View
    - Residential quads from the rear
  - 19300503WC0350b.jpg (Image 517)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from south end of Dormitories showing Group "B" Dormitory and Group "A" Dormitory extensions.
    - Campus View
    - Residential quads from the rear
  - 19300503WC0351a.jpg (Image 518)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Medical School tower, looking along main Quadrangle. On right is foundation for Physics Building.
    - Campus View
    - View from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300503WC0351b.jpg (Image 519)
    - 1930-05-03
    - View taken from Medical School tower, looking along main Quadrangle. On right is foundation for Physics Building.
    - Campus View
    - View from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300523WC0352.jpg (Image 520)
    - 1930-05-23
    - View of main campus, taken from Medical School tower.
    - Campus View
    - View from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300523WC0353.jpg (Image 521)
    - 1930-05-23
    - View showing foundation for Chemistry Building.
    - Chemistry
  - 19300604WC0354a.jpg (Image 522)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View taken from top of Medical School tower.
    - Campus View
    - looking from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300604WC0354b.jpg (Image 523)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View taken from top of Medical School tower.
    - Campus View
    - looking from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300604WC0355.jpg (Image 524)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Chapel foundation.
    - Chapel
  - 19300604WC0356.jpg (Image 525)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View showing rear of Group "B" Dormitories extension.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300604WC0357.jpg (Image 526)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View taken from top of Group "A" Dormitories showing Library in center of picture.
    - Academic
    - view of academic quad
  - 19300604WC0358.jpg (Image 527)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View showing front of Physics Building.
    - Physics
  - 19300604WC0359.jpg (Image 528)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View taken from Quadrangle showing court in front of Group "B" Dormitories.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300604WC0360.jpg (Image 529)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View taken from Union Building showing Group "A" Dormitories.
    - Craven - A
  - 19300604WC0361.jpg (Image 530)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View showing foundation for Chapel, taken from near rear of building.
    - Chapel
  - 19300604WC0362.jpg (Image 531)
    - 1930-06-04
    - View showing foundation for Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19300701WC0363a.jpg (Image 532)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View taken from Medical School tower, looking along Quadrangle.
    - Campus View
    - looking from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300701WC0363b.jpg (Image 533)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View taken from Medical School tower, looking along Quadrangle.
    - Campus View
    - looking from Davison toward Crowell
  - 19300701WC0364.jpg (Image 534)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View taken from Library tower, showing foundation for Chapel.
    - Chapel
  - 19300701WC0365.jpg (Image 535)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View taken from Group "A" Dormitory tower, showing Library, Law Building, Chemistry Building and Medical School.
    - Academic
    - view of academic quad
  - 19300701WC0366.jpg (Image 536)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View showing front of Hospital.
    - Hospital
  - 19300701WC0367.jpg (Image 537)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View showing Quadrangle in front of Chapel.
    - Campus View
    - chapel quad
  - 19300701WC0368.jpg (Image 538)
    - 1930-07-01
    - View showing Quadrangle in front of Group "B" Dormitory.
    - Crowell - B
  - 19300702WC0369.jpg (Image 539)